https://www.dailyfruitwine.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to main content
Who we are
Our website address is: https://www.dailyfruitwine.com.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Who we share your data with
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Your contact information
Additional information
How we protect your data
What data breach procedures we have in place
What third parties we receive data from
What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data
Industry regulatory disclosure requirements
Search for:
Get the Guide !
Interested in the ultimate fruit winemaking guide? Get it here:
Buy NowWinePlanet Consulting
WinePlanet Consulting, is a wine consultancy agency specializing in fruit wines, cider and mead with offices in Canada and  India to service the wine industry globally.
Contact WinePlanet with any assistance you need for your next wine project!
Get the Newsletter !Receive the "Fruit Wine News" newsletter of the fruit wine industry. Full of useful info and great winemaking tips!
Leave this field empty if you're human:
Dominic Rivard
Fruit winemaker, cider, meadmaker and industry consultant. Author of the The Ultimate Fruit Winemaker's Guide and speaker. Contact him for your wine project!
Read More
Recent Posts
Start a Winery Business in 5 Steps and live your awesome life!
The Best Fruit Wines To Try Before You Hit Your 40s
What Apple Varieties are used in Quality Craft Cider?
The Interesting History of Cider
Indian Fruit Wine – Exciting and lots to Celebrate!
Archives Archives
Select Month
October 2020  (1)
December 2019  (1)
November 2019  (2)
October 2019  (1)
November 2018  (1)
August 2018  (1)
May 2018  (1)
April 2018  (3)
February 2018  (1)
January 2018  (1)
September 2017  (2)
October 2016  (1)
September 2016  (1)
June 2016  (1)
March 2016  (2)
January 2016  (1)
December 2015  (1)
October 2015  (3)
September 2015  (1)
March 2015  (2)
January 2015  (2)
December 2014  (2)
March 2014  (1)
November 2013  (1)
August 2013  (1)
July 2013  (3)
March 2013  (1)
February 2013  (1)
November 2012  (1)
August 2012  (2)
May 2012  (2)
April 2012  (4)
January 2012  (7)
November 2011  (1)
September 2011  (1)
August 2011  (2)
July 2011  (2)
June 2011  (1)
April 2011  (2)
March 2011  (2)
February 2011  (2)
January 2011  (1)
December 2010  (3)
November 2010  (2)
September 2010  (5)
August 2010  (7)
July 2010  (4)
June 2010  (4)
May 2010  (3)
April 2010  (1)
March 2010  (3)
February 2010  (5)
January 2010  (5)
December 2009  (6)
November 2009  (5)
October 2009  (3)
September 2009  (5)
August 2009  (2)
July 2009  (4)
June 2009  (2)
May 2009  (3)
April 2009  (4)
March 2009  (4)
February 2009  (3)
January 2009  (3)
December 2008  (7)
November 2008  (9)
October 2008  (3)
September 2008  (4)
August 2008  (11)
July 2008  (5)
June 2008  (8)
May 2008  (4)
April 2008  (5)
March 2008  (9)
February 2008  (7)
January 2008  (2)
December 2007  (1)
November 2007  (9)
October 2007  (3)
September 2007  (9)
August 2007  (4)
July 2007  (5)
June 2007  (1)
May 2007  (5)
April 2007  (12)
February 2007  (1)
Meta
Log in
Entries feed
Comments feed
WordPress.org
Quick MenuHome of Fruit Wines
Help for your Wine Project
The Fruit Winemaker’s Guide
Contact Us
Privacy Policy
Site Map
Contact Me
The best way to get more information is to regularly check into www.dailyfruitwine.com with regularly updated information on fruit wine making, the industry and its development.
+1-413-551-9463
dominic@wineplanet.ca
www.dailyfruitwine.com
Contact Form
